

Demetria Cicek

UX designer

Details

Phone

+46 722 64 13 17

Email

demetria.cicek@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

Skills

Collaboration Skills

Communication Skills

Usability Testing

Adobe XD

User Research

Customer Service

UX Research

Git

HTML & CSS

React

Languages

English

• • • •

German

• • • •

Swedish

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet

Profile

Passionate about technology, humans, and psychology and how to improve customer experience. In my previous customer service roles, I pushed to make their voice heard to create a user-friendly experience. This led me later into the exciting field of UX design. I love to collaborate and exchange ideas and how to design simply yet engagingly to make things smooth.

Employment History

Content Designer, Klarna Bank AB

Oct 2020 − Present Stockholm

- Maintaining existing templates of transaction documents: updates in content and design, re-branding, fixes, adding/changing marketing blocks
- Creating, testing, and deploying new communication templates (emails, letters, push notifications) within new and existing markets in React
- Manipulating xml and json files in order to create different variations of send-outs but also for testing purposes
- Maintaining the internal Communication Library which contains a wide range of examples of send-outs, mapped out in specific dunning flows
- Collaborating with Ux writers regarding copy in send-outs, back end engineers during the implementation of send-outs and product manager

Merchant Onboarding Specialist, Klarna Bank AB

May 2019 − Oct 2020 Stockholm

- Assisting merchants with onboarding and integration of e-commerce system landscape (i.e. Magento, Shopify, API integrations)
- Checking setting errors in back-end when integration of platform failed
- Collaborating with product designers to improve the experience for merchants during the onboarding process

Education

University of Vienna, Bachelor in Linguistics

Vocational College, Diploma in Tourism

Sep 2005 − Jun 2009

Biedermannsdorf, Austria

Courses

UX design, CareerFoundry Sep 2020 – Mar 2021

Intro to Frontend development, CareerFoundry

Mar 2021 — Present